{"body":"## Summary\nImprove brownfield adoption and day-2 operations for existing Seerr installs.\n\n## Proposed changes\n- Add read-only data sources for existing singleton resources such as discover sliders and job schedules.\n- Add collection/listing data sources for brownfield discovery, especially users, jobs, and notification agents.\n- Support more natural import identifiers where possible instead of only numeric IDs.\n- Clarify or improve lifecycle semantics for singleton resources that currently remove state without resetting remote state.\n- Consider explicit adopt-only / retain-on-delete style semantics where Seerr has no real delete/reset API.\n\n## Why\nThe provider is already strong at managing known objects, but brownfield onboarding still requires too much manual discovery and import ceremony.\n\n## Scope\nThese items belong together because they all improve discoverability, importability, and lifecycle clarity for existing Seerr deployments.","title":"Improve brownfield adoption with better data sources, imports, and lifecycle semantics"}
