{"body":"## Summary\nImprove provider ergonomics so invalid configurations fail earlier and advanced usage feels more Terraform-native.\n\n## Proposed changes\n- Add schema validation for conflicting inputs such as `url` vs `hostname`/`port`/`base_url`.\n- Validate that only the matching notification-agent block is set for the selected `agent`.\n- Add provider-level operator controls such as environment-variable config, configurable request timeout, and retry/backoff behavior.\n- Make `seerr_api_object` / `seerr_api_request` easier to use by supporting structured request input and normalized JSON handling.\n- Replace or supplement raw notification bitmask UX with a typed set/list of event names.\n\n## Why\nSeveral resources currently accept ambiguous input and normalize it later, which makes plan/apply behavior harder to reason about. The generic API escape hatches also require too much raw JSON handling today.\n\n## Scope\nThis is grouped intentionally because validation, transport ergonomics, and Terraform-native schema design are all part of the same usability pass.","title":"Improve provider validation, transport options, and Terraform-native ergonomics"}
